<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Playground overview on Central Data Service Playground</title>
    <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Playground overview on Central Data Service Playground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playground overview</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-overview/</guid>
      <description>The Central Data Service Playground (CDSP) serves as a neutral, open playground for data services both within and outside the vehicle in the context of data-centric architectures. It enables investigation into the internals of these services and how they can be combined. Furthermore, the playground provides a means to publish and collaborate on such work in the open.&#xA;The playground was first conceived by the COVESA Data Architecture team to meet their needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playground logical concept</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-logical-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-logical-concept/</guid>
      <description>Importance of maintaining a logical concept COVESA is a grass roots OSS automotive alliance. From a communication and community perspective it is important to maintain descriptions of the logical concepts. Discussion at a logical level allows different parties to collaborate on common concepts, whilst making different implementation decisions, e.g. in product/technology selection or system architecture for example. That however does not mean we need spend months in philosophical discussions before moving to implementation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playground implementation</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-implementation-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-implementation-concept/</guid>
      <description>The prior section describing the logical concept should be read to understand the concepts to be implemented.&#xA;As outlined in the logical description, as a starting point the Service is realized as a basic building block combining VISS Data Server with highly functional (VSS) Data Store.&#xA;VISS data server The reference implementation for the COVESA VISS specification is developed in the VISSR project. The playground has included VISSR to provide its northbound VISS support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining with wider eco-system</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/covesa-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/covesa-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;TBA: This page will put the playground &amp;rsquo;lego piece&amp;rsquo; in context with the wider COVESA eco-system and beyond, e.g. connection to CVI/Capabilities/Vehicle API gateway southbound&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
