<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Central Data Service Playground</title>
    <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Central Data Service Playground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playground overview</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-overview/</guid>
      <description>The Central Data Service Playground (CDSP) serves as a neutral, open playground for data services both within and outside the vehicle in the context of data-centric architectures. It enables investigation into the internals of these services and how they can be combined. Furthermore, the playground provides a means to publish and collaborate on such work in the open.&#xA;The playground was first conceived by the COVESA Data Architecture team to meet their needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playground logical concept</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-logical-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-logical-concept/</guid>
      <description>Importance of maintaining a logical concept COVESA is a grass roots OSS automotive alliance. From a communication and community perspective it is important to maintain descriptions of the logical concepts. Discussion at a logical level allows different parties to collaborate on common concepts, whilst making different implementation decisions, e.g. in product/technology selection or system architecture for example. That however does not mean we need spend months in philosophical discussions before moving to implementation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playground implementation</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-implementation-concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/cdsp-implementation-concept/</guid>
      <description>The prior section describing the logical concept should be read to understand the concepts to be implemented.&#xA;As outlined in the logical description, as a starting point the Service is realized as a basic building block combining VISS Data Server with highly functional (VSS) Data Store.&#xA;VISS data server The reference implementation for the COVESA VISS specification is developed in the VISSR project. The playground has included VISSR to provide its northbound VISS support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining with wider eco-system</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/covesa-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/overview/covesa-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;TBA: This page will put the playground &amp;rsquo;lego piece&amp;rsquo; in context with the wider COVESA eco-system and beyond, e.g. connection to CVI/Capabilities/Vehicle API gateway southbound&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apache IoTDB</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/manuals/apache-iotdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/manuals/apache-iotdb/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The playground uses Apache IoTDB to provide a highly functional data store.&#xA;Description of Apache IoTDB from https://iotdb.apache.org/:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Apache IoTDB (Database for Internet of Things) is an IoT native database with high performance for data management and analysis, deployable on the edge and the cloud. Due to its light-weight architecture, high performance and rich feature set together with its deep integration with Apache Hadoop, Spark and Flink, Apache IoTDB can meet the requirements of massive data storage, high-speed data ingestion and complex data analysis in the IoT industrial fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISSR (VISS data server)</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/manuals/vissr-viss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/cdsp/manuals/vissr-viss/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The playground uses the VISSR project to provide its northbound VISS support, along with the other features it provides.&#xA;The VISSR project documentation site has extensive documentation on the VISSR components. So as the project progresses we will add information below focused on topics specific to the playground.&#xA;Apache IoTDB connector Please see the IoTDB guide for details of the connector between VISSR and IoTDB.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
